[
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Raw Materials",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 3,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -2,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Direct Materials",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Prepaid Advertising",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Prepaid Expenses",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 3,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -2,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Prepaid Salary",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "event",
    "question": "Menipu atasan Anda dengan memberikan keterangan palsu dalam laporan keuangan sehingga mendapat hukuman mundur 34 langkah",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -34,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Prepaid Rent",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Work in Process",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 3,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -2,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Finished Goods",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Debt Investments",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  }
]
